John W. Ryan papers, 1950-2011 C458
Indiana University Archives
- Organizations, 1961-1993; undated
  - American Society for Public Administration (ASPA), 1961-1983; undated
    - Miscellaneous (Box 7)
      - President's Personal ASPA File, 1972 (Box 9)
      - President's Speeches, undated (Box 9)
      - President's Travel, 1972 (Box 9)
      - Public Service, 1974 (Box 9)
      - Standing Committee on Higher Education - Governmental Relationships, 1973 (Box 9)
      - Standing Committee on Public Policy Affecting Public Administration, 1973 (Box 9)
      - Task Force on Interrelating the Needs of Government and Universities, 1973 (Box 9)
      - University Finances, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Indiana Bell Telephone Company, 1973-1984; undated
    - Financial Management of Company Pension Plans, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Pension Fund Advisory Committee, 1974; (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Energy Conservation, 1974-1975 (Box 9)
    - Pension Funds, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Pension Fund Advisory Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
    - Pension Fund, September 1976 (Box 9)
    - Basketball Tip-off Luncheon, November 1976 (Box 9)
    - General, 1976 (Box 9)
    - Columbia Club, December 1976 (Box 9)
    - Pamphlets and Newspapers, 1976-1978 (Box 9)
    - San Diego, February 1977 (Box 9)
    - January – June 1977 (Box 9)
    - July – December 1977 (Box 10)
    - 1978 (Box 10)
    - Board Minutes, January 1978 (Box 10)
    - Board Book, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Board Minutes, February 1978 (Box 10)
    - Board, March 1978 (Box 10)
    - Pension Fund and Board Meeting, May 1978 (Box 10)
    - Board, June 1978 (Box 10)
    - Meeting, July 1978 (Box 10)
    - August 1978 (Box 10)
    - Meeting, September 1978 (Box 10)
    - Board, October 1978 (Box 10)
    - Meeting, November 1978 (Box 10)
    - Board Meeting, December 1978 (Box 10)
    - Pension Funds, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
    - Brochures, 1979 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, January – June 1979 (Box 10)
    - Board Meeting, January 1979 (Box 10)
    - Pension Fund Advisory Committee, January 1979 (Box 10)
    - Board (Box 10)
      - February 1979 (Box 10)
      - March 1979 (Box 10)
      - April 1979 (Box 10)
      - May 1979, (2 folders) (Box 10)
      - June 1979 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, July – December 1979 (Box 10)
      - July 1979 (Box 10)
      - August 1979 (Box 10)
      - September 1979 (Box 10)
      - October 1979 (Box 10)
    - Board (Box 10)
    - Pension Fund, November 1979 (Box 10)
    - Board, November 1979 (Box 10)
    - General, 1979-1983 (Box 10)
    - Board, January 1980 (Box 10)
    - Pension Advisory Board, February 1980 (Box 10)
    - Board (Box 10)
      - March 1980 (Box 10)
      - April 1980 (Box 10)
      - May 1980 (Box 10)
      - June 1980 (Box 10)
      - July 1980 (Box 10)
    - Organization, undated (Box 10)
    - General, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Pension Fund, 1980 (Box 10)
    - General, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Board (Box 10)
      - September 1980 (Box 10)
      - October 1980 (Box 10)
      - November 1980 (Box 11)
      - December 1980 (Box 11)
    - General, 1980 (Box 11)
    - Board (Box 11)
      - January 1981 (Box 11)
      - February 1981 (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
    - Board of Directors, February 1981 (Box 11)
    - Corporate Public Policy Committee, February 1981 (Box 11)
    - Board, March 1981 (Box 11)
    - Pension Fund Advisory Committee, March 1981 (Box 11)
    - General, March 1981 (Box 11)
    - Schulhof, Weiss, Ryan Meeting, April 1981 (Box 11)
    - Bell Board - Meridian, April 1981 (Box 11)
    - General, May 1981 (Box 11)
    - Board Meeting, June 1981 (Box 11)
    - Board (Box 11)
      - July 1981 (Box 11)
      - August 1981 (Box 11)
      - September 1981, (2 folders) (Box 11)
      - October 1981 (Box 11)
    - Corporate Public Policy Committee, October 1981 (Box 11)
    - Board, December 1981 (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Board, January 1982 (Box 11)
    - General, February 1982 (Box 11)
    - Board, March 1982 (Box 11)
    - Board, May 1982 (Box 11)
    - Corporate Public Policy Committee Meeting, July 1982 (Box 11)
    - Board, July 1982 (Box 11)
    - Bell Seminar - Allentown, PA, September 1982 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, December 1982 (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 11)
    - General, January 1983 (Box 11)
    - Corporate Public Policy, Bell Board, February 1983 (Box 11)
    - Board, March 1983 (Box 11)
    - Board, May 1983 (Box 11)
    - Corporate Public Policy, June 1983 (Box 11)
    - General, July 1983 (Box 11)
    - Corporate Public Policy, Bell Board, November 1983 (Box 11)
    - Board of Directors, December 1983 (Box 12)
    - Bell Board, December 1983 (Box 12)
    - General, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Board Meeting, January 1984 (Box 12)
    - Bell Board Executive Committee Preceding Board Meeting, February 1984 (Box 12)
  - College of St. Thomas, 1972-1984
    - Alumni Coeducational Survey, 1972-1976 (Box 12)
    - Board of Trustees, October 1975 (Box 12)
    - January 1976 (Box 12)
    - February 1976 (Box 12)
    - Annual Board Meeting, October 1976 (Box 12)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, October 1976 (Box 12)
    - General, 1976 (Box 12)
    - Off Campus Program, 1976-1977 (Box 12)
    - Board of Trustees, April 1977 (Box 12)
    - Commencement, May 1977 (Box 12)
    - Board of Trustees, October 1977 (Box 12)
    - John Grenzebach & Associates, December 1977 (Box 12)
    - Publications, 1977-1980 (Box 12)
    - January 1978 (Box 12)
    - Board of Trustees, April 1978 (Box 12)
    - Fund Drive, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Board of Trustees, December 1978 (Box 12)
    - December 1978 (Box 12)
    - Case Statement: Priorities for the 80's Campaign, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Development Study, 1978 (Box 12)
    - 1978-1985 (Box 12)
    - Board, March 1979 (Box 12)
    - Board, June 1979 (Box 12)
    - October 1979 (Box 12)
    - November 1979 (Box 12)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 12)
    - February 1980 (Box 12)
    - MBA Review Committee and Academic Affairs Committee, June 1980 (Box 12)
    - June 1980 (Box 13)
    - September 1980 (Box 13)
    - October 1980, (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Correspondence and Minutes, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Academic Student Affairs Meeting, March 1981 (Box 13)
    - Board of Trustees, March 1981 (Box 13)
    - Board of Trustees, June 1981 (Box 13)
    - Board of Trustees, October 1981 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 13)
    - General, 1981-1982 (Box 13)
    - Board of Trustees, June 1982 (Box 13)
    - General, 1982-1983 (Box 13)
    - Board of Trustees, October 1983 (Box 13)
    - General, 1983-1984 (Box 13)
    - Board of Trustees, March 1984 (Box 13)
    - Board of Trustees, May 1984 (Box 13)
    - Committee on Academic and Student Affairs, May 1984 (Box 13)
  - State Life Insurance Company, 1977-1985
    - 1977-1980 (Box 13)
    - May 1979 (Box 13)
    - November 1979 (Box 13)
    - 1979-1983 (Box 13)
    - January 1980 (Box 13)
    - February 1980 (Box 13)
    - Board, May 1980 (Box 13)
    - July 1980 (Box 13)
    - November 1980 (Box 13)
    - February 1981 (Box 13)
    - May 1981 (Box 13)
    - August 1981 (Box 13)
    - November 1981 (Box 13)
    - 1981-1983 (Box 13)
    - February 1982 (Box 13)
    - May 1982 (Box 13)
    - August 1982 (Box 13)
    - November 1982 (Box 14)
    - General, 1982 (Box 14)
    - February 1983 (Box 14)
    - 1983, (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - Long Range Planning, 1983 (Box 14)
    - Audit Committee, November 1983 (Box 14)
    - Policyholders' Meeting, January 1984 (Box 14)
    - February 1984 (Box 14)
    - May 1984 (Box 14)
    - August 1984 (Box 14)
    - October 1984 (Box 14)
    - 1985 (Box 14)
  - General, 1972-1986
    - American Fletcher National Bank (AFNB) (Box 14)
      - General, 1984 (Box 14)
      - Board, February 1984 (Box 14)
      - Board, March 1984 (Box 14)
      - Audit Committee, Board Meeting, June 1984 (Box 14)
      - Executive and Board Meeting, July 1984 (Box 14)
      - Joint Meeting Audit, AFC and Examining Committees, December 1984 (Box 14)
    - Corporate Community Council (Box 14)
      - Steering Committee (Box 14)
        - September 1978 (Box 14)
        - October 1978 (Box 14)
        - December 1978 (Box 14)
      - Steering Committee Lilly Endowment, April 1979 (Box 14)
      - General, July 1979 (Box 14)
      - Steering Committee, 1979 (Box 14)
      - Board of Directors, 1979 (Box 14)
      - General, November 1979 (Box 14)
      - Lilly Endowment, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
      - General (Box 14)
        - March 1980 (Box 14)
        - April 1980 (Box 14)
        - May 1980 (Box 14)
        - June 1980 (Box 14)
        - October 1980 (Box 14)
      - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 14)
      - Board (Box 14)
        - April 1981 (Box 14)
        - November 1981 (Box 14)
      - General (Box 14)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 14)
        - 1981-1983 (Box 14)
      - Board of Directors Lilly Endowment, June 1986 (Box 14)
    - Indiana Society for Public Administration (ISPA) (Box 14)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 14)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 14)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 14)
    - National Academy of Public Administrators (NAPA) (Box 14)
      - Member Certificate, 1972 (Box 14)
      - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 14)
      - Meeting, May 1976 (Box 14)
      - General (Box 14)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 14)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 15)
        - 1978 (Box 15)
        - 1979 (Box 15)
        - 1979-1981 (Box 15)
        - 1980, (2 folders) (Box 15)
        - 1981 (Box 15)
        - 1982 (Box 15)
    - National Institution of Public Management (Box 15)
      - 1976-1978 (Box 15)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 15)
- Speeches, 1958-1968
  - General Speech Material, 1958-1967; (4 folders) (Box 15)
  - Liberal Arts, 1962-1964 (Box 15)
  - Frontier Regional High School, June 11, 1963 (Box 15)
  - Rotary Speech-Bloomington to Bangkok, November 26, 1963 (Box 15)
  - Speech to Alumni, December 1, 1963 (Box 15)
  - Kappa Delta Pi Speech, January 7, 1964 (Box 15)
  - Speech to Education Faculty, February 27, 1964 (Box 15)
  - Information Systems for Creative Mgmt. Conference, March 1964 (Box 15)
  - Student Government Day, October 1, 1964 (Box 15)
  - Salt Lake Alumni, October 24, 1964 (Box 15)
  - American Association of University Women (AAUW), November 14, 1964 (Box 15)
  - Newman Club Speech, ca. 1964 (Box 15)
  - Sperry-Phoenix, ca. 1964 (Box 15)
  - Implications Of Religion in University Life, ca. 1964 (Box 15)
  - Guild of Lay Theologians, May 21, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Opening Student Convocation, September 23, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Speech to "Four H", October 1, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Laying of Cornerstone at Salem State College, November 2, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Honors Convocation, November 8, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Student Government Conference, November 19, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Junior Chamber of Commerce, January 25, 1966; (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Arizona State University Speech, April 30, 1966 (Box 15)
  - Alumni Awards Luncheon, June 11, 1966 (Box 15)
  - University of Massachusetts Alumni, Essex County, November 10, 1966 (Box 15)
  - Urban Grant University Funding Convocation, December 10, 1966 (Box 15)
  - Commencement Speech-Cardinal Cushing College, May 30, 1967 (Box 15)
  - Chancellor's Speech to Freshmen, September 18, 1967 (Box 15)
  - Charitable Irish Society Speech, March 17, 1968 (Box 15)
  - Lutheran Speech, April 6, 1968 (Box 15)
  - Annual Institute of ASPA, April 11, 1968 (Box 15)
  - Dean Junior College, April 17, 1968 (Box 15)
  - Honors Convocation Speech, May 14, 1968 (Box 15)
  - Address to Student Body, May 16, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Alumni College Talk, June 8, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Mass Bay, June 9, 1968 (Box 16)
- Course and Research files, 1950-1988; undated
  - Indiana University, 1950-1988; undated
    - American National Government G104 – Lecture Notes, 1953 (Box 16)
    - Economics E563, 1957; emph: RESTRICTED (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1952-1958 (Box 16)
    - Municipal Government, 1952 (Box 16)
    - Notebook – Government of China (G463 and G815), 1953 (Box 16)
    - Political Science 123 – Notebook, 1950-1951; (Restricted Records Removed) (Box 16)
    - Politics of Higher Education, ca. 1988 (Box 16)
    - Public Finance (E360) and Management (P500), 1953; (Restricted Records Removed) (Box 16)
    - University of Thammasat, Bangkok, Thailand (Box 16)
      - Bangkok Municipality – Thailand, 1955 (Box 16)
      - Final Reports, 1956-1959 (Box 16)
      - Intensive Language Training Program, undated (Box 16)
      - Local Government in Thailand, 1957; (3 folders) (Box 16)
      - Local Government Date and Documents, 1955 (Box 16)
      - Klausner Report, 1956 (Box 16)
      - National Government Data and Documents, 1956-1960 (Box 16)
      - Program for Strengthening Public Administration in the Kingdom of Thailand, 1952 (Box 16)
      - Semi-Annual Reports, 1957-1959 (Box 16)
      - Some Notes on Thai Customs, 1956 (Box 16)
      - Summary Statement – Evaluation of the Indiana – Thammasat Contract, 1960 (Box 16)
      - Thailand Evaluation – Miscellaneous Working Papers, 1959-1960; (2 folders) (Box 16)
      - Miscellaneous, 1960; undated; (3 folders) (Box 17)
  - University of Wisconsin, 1955-1963; undated
    - Administrative Self- Analysis, undated (Box 17)
    - American Society for Public Administration (ASAP) – Reading Materials, 1960 (Box 17)
    - Communication, 1960-1961 (Box 17)
    - Comparative Administration, 1961 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 17)
    - Financial Administration, 1959-1961 (Box 17)
    - Finance – Organization and Administration, 1957-1961 (Box 17)
    - Human Relations in Administration, 1959-1960 (Box 17)
    - Management Audit, 1961 (Box 17)
    - Management Controls, 1961 (Box 17)
    - Materials for Case Problems, 1958-1961 (Box 17)
    - Municipal Autonomy or Consolidation for the City of St. Francis, 1960 (Box 17)
    - Municipal Management Course, 1957 (Box 17)
    - Organization, 1960-1961 (Box 17)
    - Policy Training for Delinquency Prevention, 1961 (Box 17)
    - Political Science 7a (Box 17)
      - Topic Files (Box 17)
        - National Defense, 1961 (Box 17)
        - Financing National Government, undated (Box 17)
    - Political Science 7b (Box 17)
      - General, 1961; emph: RESTRICTED (Box 17)
      - Topic Files, 1955-1963; undated (Box 17)
        - Federal System, 1955-1961 (Box 17)
        - Interstate Relations, undated (Box 17)
        - State Constitutions, 1960 (Box 17)
        - Nomination Campaign, Election, 1961-1962 (Box 17)
        - Parties, 1961-1962 (Box 17)
        - Electorate Pressure Groups, 1960 (Box 17)
        - State Legislators, 1959-1961 (Box 17)
        - The Governor, 1959-1962 (Box 17)
        - State Administrative Organization, 1955-1961 (Box 17)
        - Personnel, 1961 (Box 17)
        - Revenue, 1960-1963 (Box 17)
        - Budget Expenditure, 1957-1962 (Box 17)
        - Courts, 1959-1961 (Box 17)
        - Law Enforcement, 1953-1961 (Box 17)
        - Education, 1960-1962 (Box 17)
        - Education-Rural Youth, 1959-1963 (Box 17)
        - Health and Welfare, 1961 (Box 17)
        - State Highway Administration, 1960-1961 (Box 17)
      - Exams and Outlines, 1960-1963 (Box 17)
      - Final Examination, 1962 (Box 17)
    - Political Science 143, Exams, 1960-1961; (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - Public Administration in Agricultural Development, 1961; (3 folders) (Box 18)
    - Public Administration Short Course, 1959-1960; (3 folders) (Box 18)
    - Public Relations, 1958-1959 (Box 18)
    - Public Welfare, 1958 (Box 18)
    - The Wisconsin State Fair: Its Modern Role and Objectives, 1960 (Box 18)
  - Arizona State University and University of Massachusetts, 1962-1968; undated
    - Government and Politics of Japan, undated (Box 18)
    - Governments of the Far East (PS 475g) (Box 18)
      - General, 1964-1965; (4 folders) (Restricted Records Removed) (Box 18)
      - Exams, 1964 (Box 18)
      - Graduate Student Submitted Exams Questions, 1963-1964 (Box 18)
      - Lecture Outline, undated (Box 18)
      - Recommended Readings, undated (Box 18)
      - Sino-Japanese Relations, undated (Box 18)
      - Student Papers, 1965; emph: RESTRICTED (Box 18)
    - Indian Administrator's Program, 1964 (Box 18)
    - Indonesia Lectures, 1963 (Box 18)
    - Manuscript – Cultural Values and Public Administration, 1964; emph: RESTRICTED (Box 18)
    - Parents Questionnaires, 1963-1968 (Box 18)
    - Eleanor Roehr, emph: RESTRICTED (Box 18)
      - Urban Government and Administration, 1962-1963 (Box 18)
      - Papers on India and Tokyo, 1962-1963 (Box 18)
    - Urban University Symposium, 1966 (Box 18)
- Correspondence and personal files, 1965-2011
  - Alumni Association – 50 Year Reunion, 2008 (Box 18)
  - Congratulatory Letters (Box 18)
    - Appointment to Chancellor of the University of Massachusetts, 1965 (Box 18)
    - Investiture, 1972 (Box 18)
    - On Becoming President (A-K), 1971 (Box 18)
    - On Becoming President (L-Z), 1971 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 18)
  - Personal files (Box 18)
    - 1963-1969 (Box 18)
  - Ryan Scholarship – Leadership Award, 2008-2011 (Box 18)
  - SUNY: Governor, State of New York, 2000-2003 (Box 18)
    - 1968-1970 (Box 19)
    - 1971 (Box 19)
    - 1972 (Box 19)
  - Restricted files (Box 20)